Good morning.
good morning
Unannounced.
Unannounced?
Clothes check.
Clothes check?
This is what I'm wearing today.
What's the point of today's outfit?
I'm trying to look stylish.
That's all.
That's all. Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Good morning.
I'm Meinouchi.
Check out my outfit.
I'm eating so many Mintias.
Good morning.
Check out my outfit.
What's today's outfit?
Like this.
This is...
Today.
Really...
Mintia, I'm sorry.
I've already filmed for Youtube.
Today's point is...
I don't have much left to say.
This is it.
I designed this bag myself.
I also
I use it on a regular basis.
What do you think?
I don't remember the top one, but the bottom oneI don't remember the top one for a minute, but the bottom one is...
Um, Lily Brown.
And, um, these are shoes.
I was thinking about what to do today,
I recently went to, uh, Girls Guides to buy myself a costume for LilyBrown.
So I have the costumes at home.
I wore the costumes.
I'm using them as if they were my own. I'm sorry.
Yes, well, this is, uh, this is, uh..,
Bakehawa, I don't know where it's from, like Beltim.
I'm really sorry.
I bought it in Zodotown.
I buy at Zodotown, so I buy at Zodotown all the time.
Yes, that's all.
That's all.
That's all. Thank you very much.
Okay, I'm going to get ready for the photo shoot.
Bye bye.
Good morning.
Here's a check of the nuki-uchi's personal clothes.
Oh, wow.
Clothes are not much clothes.
It's not much of an outfit.
Well, let's start with you, Claire.
I'm just so-so, because it's summer, and it's a pointy summer for clothes,
I'm thinking that it would be better if the legs were slightly open,
I'm thinking that it would be better if the bust was open a little bit, but not too much.
I just put on a pair of jeans that were hanging in the laundry and in my room.
Oh, I'm in the middle of a nuki-striking session.
Oh, did you do it?
I already did it.
I heard he already did it.
What do you think I should do? Point.What do you suggest we do about it? Point.
I made it simple.
We kept it simple.
I recommend these headphones.
I recommend them.
Please buy them, everyone.
Oh, I matched the black of the headphones with the black of the shoes.
It's definitely not the same.
And they are costume shoes.
Don't tell me.
I said it first.
They're costume shoes.
Costume shoes.
But I also said no bag,
I came with "simple is best.
I brought my bag, just in case.
Thank you very much.
But I didn't bring an umbrella today, so I came here soaking wet.
Oh, you got wet?
I was embarrassed on the train because it was so obvious that I was so wet.
Don't worry. I'm not wet now.
That's right. It's dry now.
That's good, that's good.
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
I'm hitting the ground running.
Yes, sir.
I'm checking out my clothes.
Personal Clothes?
What's the point of today's outfit?
What?
Today is August.
I've been thinking of a summery look.
I've been into flared outfits lately.I've been into a bit of a flare-ish thing lately.
so I decided to go with something like this.
But I wanted something a little more casual
jeans and sneakers.
I forgot this.
This, this is Zara.
This is, what was it?
Michael Kors.
That's all.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
Unannounced personal effects check.
Clothes check.
Is that a new thing?
Yes, today.
I'll go first.
Well...
Today.
It's summer, so it's easy.
I wore a one-piece dress.
because it's summer and it's easy.
Well, a one-piece...
Like a poppin
at the place
and
This jacket is from Korea.
Korean
brand
and
And the bag is by Mark Deacon.
I have all of these.
This is a gift from a fan.Yes, this is a necklace given to me by a fan.
I got this necklace from a fan.
The dress and the flower pattern match.
The floral pattern matches with the dress.
I put it on.
I don't have a theme in mind.
but I've been wearing a tiny inner layer recently.
I've been doing that.
As a point of reference, I added this...
What's this?
It's not a vest.
I'm wearing a vest.
First of all, he's wearing martins, and this is...
This is...
I went to a place called Betty Smith in Ebisu to make jeans.
I made these myself when I was on location there.
When I went to Clearto
This is Maujyu's belt.
Inside this is Ape's innerwear.
This is Betty.
Everyone has one of these.
I have this one.
This is Jesus.
It's very old and dirty.
This is the one with the "yes" on it.
The bottom is cute!
Yay!
I don't know if this is okay.
It's very rough.
That's all for now.
Good morning.
Milk shift check.
I see.
This is how it's going to be today.This is what it looks like today.
What is the point of the coordination?
My image is to wear cool summer clothes.
Today, I'm going for a reddish look.
This is the exragin
And this is Hiss.
This is hiss, too.
And this is hiss.
And here's a hiss from Adides
Here's a timber
Yes, it was like this. Bye-bye.